Ricardo Humberto Sá

(437) 240-8284 Toronto, ON <u>r.humberto.sa@gmail.com</u>

www.linkedin.com/in/ricardohsa

Technically skilled, results-oriented, and an impeccable work ethic. An individual who is confident and poised in interactions with co-workers and clients at all levels. Experience with creating, customize software and provide support for final users.

Areas of Expertise:

- C#
- ASP .NET MVC 5
- VB.Net

- Entity Framework
- Web Services
- Web API
- Oracle SQL

- Agile
- Javascript
- JQuery
- Angular 7

CAREER HISTORY

SysOpen, São Paulo, Brazil

January 2018 - November 2018

Web Developer

- Using the framework Scrum, on two-week sprints
- Supporting ASP.NET MVC 5 using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery
- Developing database schemas as well as stored procedures using Microsoft SQL Server
- Creating a new WCF REST service
- Providing support for legacy web application code developed C#, PL/SQL and T-SQL
- Creating and maintain support documentation
- Programming and debugging SPA/ASP.NET-based web applications

Conductor, São Paulo, Brazil

October 2016 - December 2017

Web Developer/System Analyst

- Using the framework Scrum, on two-week sprints
- Creating new backend features using C# and VB.net .net Framework 3.5 and support for legacy web application code developed C# and ASP.net WebForms.
- Applying Web Services, WCF and WebApi.
- Performing tables, views functions and procedures in SQL Server using T-SQL
- Providing reports using SQL Server Reporting Services
- Supporting existing WCF services including new SOAP methods

Amil UHG, São Paulo, Brasil

January 2015 – October 2016

System Developer

- Debugging Code to create hotfixes using C# and PL/SQL for issues reported by the PO
- Creating and updating tables, functions, procedures, and views with T-SQL and PL/SQL in SQL Server and Oracle
- Creating new ASP.NET MVC pages using HTML, Bootstrap, jQuery, and JavaScript and Entity Framework in internal projects

System Analyst

- Scrum Master
- Programming using C#, Delphi 7.0 and T-SQL
- Creating new backend features using C# and VB.net .net Framework 3.5 and support for legacy web application code developed C# and ASP.net WebForms.
- Team Leader for Software Factory Project Packages. Responsible for coordinating and monitoring development

Metallurgical Albras, São Paulo, Brazil

October 2004 – October 2009

System Administrator

• Installed, configured and administered Windows XP, 7 2000, Active Directory.

FORMAL EDUCATION AND CREDENTIALS

PSM I – Professional Scrum Master 2018
IBTA – Instituto Brasileiro de Tecnologia Avançada 2010

Postgraduate in Software Engineering/SOA

UNIB – Universidade IbirapueraBacharel in Computer Science

2002